gamedesire.com 2006-10-22

# GameDesire - play free online games. Snooker, pool, mahjong, card games.

**Privacy policy**

To play games on GameDesire, Ganymede Technologies requests that you register and create an account with a nickname which is the name you will be known by to others players. During this registration process, GameDesire asks for personal information, which Ganymede Technologies will use in accordance with this Privacy Policy. GameDesire also requests your e-mail address so that Ganymede Technologies may contact you.

All registrations become the exclusive property of Ganymede Technologies. Ganymede Technologies reserves the right to use and reuse all registration information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Members may edit, update, or delete their registrations without limitation, at any time and as often as desired.

Ganymede Technologies will not intentionally disclose any personally identifying information about you to third parties without your consent, except where Ganymede Technologies in good faith, believe such disclosure is necessary to comply with the law or to enforce Terms of Service of GameDesire. Certain information about you may be given to GameDesire Administrators. This information is used by them to enforce Terms of Service and may include your nick, IP address and unique ID that your computer receives when you start playing games in GameDesire. This way they can determine what other nicks have been registered using this specific computer and take appropriate actions if necessary.

By registering for an account, you agree that GameDesire may display your login and the name of the game you last played, as well as your game rankings and scores. You also agree that GameDesire may display date and time of your last visit to our service as well as date and time when your account was created.

You are given the privilege to define the content of an optional info page containing your photo, age and short description of your personal interests. All such information is optional and everything you enter and make visible will be visible to other users of the GameDesire. Ganymede Technologies urges you to be careful only to enter information that you are comfortable sharing with the public at large. You may edit, delete, or modify that information at any time.

Certain information about your computer hardware and software is automatically collected by theGameDesire. This information may include: your IP address, unique identification number based on hardware and software components of the computer, browser type and operating system, hardware and software components of your computer. This information is used by Ganymede Technologies for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the GameDesire.

Cookies are small files downloaded to your computer to track movements within web sites. Like most entertainment and gaming sites, GameDesire also uses cookies to track your visits to the site so that you do not have to re-register each time you visit us. They also allow GameDesire to understand how you use our service and how Ganymede Technologies can improve the site.

We reserve the right to change this policy from time to time, so please check here from time to time to see if there is a revised policy available.

We have made a tremendous effort to ensure the security of our users. As such, you can have a high degree of confidence that the personal information you give GameDesire is protected from unauthorized access and use.

Ganymede Technologies cautions you against giving out personally identifiable information (such as social security numbers, credit card numbers, names and addresses, telephone numbers, driver license numbers) to strangers online, as this information may be used for illegal or harmful purposes.

We strongly encourage you to protect your information by creating a long and not easy to guess password. Such password should not resemble your name or any other personal information regarding you and preferably should contain capital letters and numbers.

You are able to [edit your personal data](http://www.gamedesire.com/dd-1,n-1.html) after logging in, you can also [remove your account](http://www.gamedesire.com/dd-1,n-7.html) including all personal data. If you think that somebody gained unauthorised access to your data, please [contact us](http://www.gamedesire.com/dd-4,n-8.html). 

We use third-party advertising companies and advertising networks to serve ads to you on our behalf when you visit our Web site.   
These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp.
